<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Live Slider</string>
    <string name="toast_sensor_error">Sorry! This device does not support Rotation Vector Sensor.</string>
    <string name="toast_invalid_pic_path">Invalid picture path!</string>
    <string name="toast_failed_set_picture">Setting failed. Please retry!</string>
    <string name="toast_failed_launch_wallpaper_chooser">Couldn\'t launch wallpaper chooser. You can still activate Live Slider by choosing \"Live Wallpapers\" in your home screen wallpaper picker.</string>

    <string name="introduction1">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="introduction2">
        <![CDATA[
            This Live Wallpaper can produce a parallax effect by slightly offsetting the position of the wallpaper.<br>
            *It is required to obtain the device\'s rotation angle data from <b>Rotation Vector Sensor</b> in real time. You can check whether your device supports the sensor by rotating the device and seeing whether the cube below changes its perspective.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="picture">Picture</string>
    <string name="picture_default">Default</string>
    <string name="picture_custom">Custom</string>
    <string name="range">Range</string>
    <string name="delay">Speed</string>
    <string name="scroll">Wallpaper scrolling</string>
    <string name="power_save">Pause in battery saver mode</string>
    <string name="activate">Activate</string>
    <string name="wallpapers_slideshow">Wallpapers Slideshow</string>
    <string name="settings_preview">Settings Preview</string>
    <string name="select_playlist">Please select a wallpapers playlist to enable slideshow!</string>
    <string name="change_wallpaper">Change Wallpaper</string>
    <string name="wallpaper_settings">Wallpaper Settings</string>
    <string name="thumbnail">thumbnail</string>
    <string name="playlist_activation">You can activate and edit wallpapers in this playlist right here and any previous selected wallpaper will be changed respectively. </string>
    <string name="single_wallpaper_alert">Are you sure you want to disable current Playlist slideshow and continue with current single wallpaper selection…</string>
    <string name="change_wallpapers">Change Wallpapers</string>
    <string name="change_current_wallpaper">Change current wallpaper</string>
    <string name="double_tap_wallpaper">Double Tap Wallpaper</string>
    <string name="wallpaper_slideshow">Wallpaper Slideshow</string>
    <string name="wallpaper_changes_after_some_time">Wallpaper changes after some time</string>
    <string name="pause_everything_in_battery_saver_mode">Pause everything in battery saver mode</string>
    <string name="power_saver_mode">Power Saver Mode</string>
    <string name="enable_to_get_scroll_effect">Enable to get scroll effect</string>
    <string name="wallpaper_scrolling">Wallpaper Scrolling</string>
    <string name="photos">Photos</string>
    <string name="_100">100+</string>
    <string name="na">NA</string>
    <string name="march">March</string>
    <string name="date">24</string>
    <string name="add_wallpaper">add wallpaper</string>
    <string name="no_empty_time">Slideshow time must be at least 3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="front_face">FRONT FACE</string>
    <string name="default_face">DEFAULT</string>
    <string name="default_calibration">Default</string>
    <string name="vertical_calibration">Vertical</string>
    <string name="dynamic_calibration">Dynamic</string>
    <string name="active">ACTIVE</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back Button</string>

    <!-- Help Dialog Strings -->
    <string name="help_dialog_title">Help &amp; Information</string>
    <string name="help_settings_controls_title">Settings Controls:</string>
    <string name="help_range_info">• Range: Controls the intensity of the parallax effect by zooming the image. Higher values create more movement as the image is translated more on sensor movements, but the image becomes more zoomed for greater bias range. The lowest value (0) completely shuts off the parallax animation with no sensor updates, while slideshow will still work normally.</string>
    <string name="help_speed_info">• Speed: Adjusts how quickly the wallpaper responds to device rotation. Higher values make parallax react faster. For normal movements, smoothing is added as device sensor rotation values are not linear to tackle jittery effects. At maximum speed, there is no smoothing - if your device has a good sensor you may not see jittery effects, otherwise you know the drill.</string>
    <string name="help_power_saver_info">• Power Saver Mode: Pauses all wallpaper effects when battery saver is enabled to conserve battery life.</string>
    <string name="help_slideshow_info">• Wallpaper Slideshow: Automatically changes wallpapers from your selected playlist at set intervals. Minimum time interval is 3 seconds for performance reasons and inbuilt Android battery optimizations that freeze update callbacks for animations.</string>
    <string name="help_double_tap_info">• Double Tap Wallpaper: Allows changing wallpapers by double-tapping the screen for quick wallpaper switching.</string>
    <string name="help_calibration_modes_title">Calibration Modes:</string>
    <string name="help_default_calibration">• Default: Sets the parallax face as default wherever your phone is facing at the moment. The wallpaper will animate with respect to that initial position. Simple calibration that works well for basic parallax effects.</string>
    <string name="help_vertical_calibration">• Vertical: Considers only 2 faces where ground and sky positions are detected. Perfect for users who mainly use their phone facing upwards during normal day usage and facing downwards when lying on the bed. Only recalibrates when switching between upright and upside-down orientations.</string>
    <string name="help_dynamic_calibration">• Dynamic: Advanced mode that considers all 6 faces of the cube as possibilities. Wherever your phone is facing, the parallax wallpaper origin will update automatically based on the current phone direction (portrait, landscape, flat positions). Provides the most adaptive experience with automatic face detection and recalibration.</string>
    <string name="help_cube_helper">A helper cube is displayed that shows your current active face position as reference.</string>
    <string name="help_got_it">Got it</string>
    
    <!-- Transition Settings -->
    <string name="transition_effect">Transition Effect</string>
    <string name="transition_effect_description">Choose wallpaper transition style</string>
    <string name="transition_speed">Transition Speed</string>
    <string name="transition_speed_description">How fast wallpapers change</string>
    <string name="transition_mode_fade_to_black">Fade to Black</string>
    <string name="transition_mode_crossfade">Crossfade</string>
    <string name="transition_speed_slow">Slow</string>
    <string name="transition_speed_normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="transition_speed_fast">Fast</string>
    <string name="transition_speed_very_fast">Very Fast</string>
</resources>